marico.com 2019-01-12

# Marico – make a difference

**Scope**

We value and respect your Privacy. This Marico Privacy Policy (Privacy Policy) describes the information collected by Marico and how we use and protect this information. Our Privacy Policy practices are consistent with the Information Technology (Amendment) Act, 2008 and adoption of amendments as and when notified subject to its applicability. 

**Terms of Use**

Your use of this portal is also subject to the [Terms of Use ](https://marico.com/other/terms-of-use) posted on this web-portal. 

**Information Covered by this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Statement applies to personal information collected by Marico. 

Personal information is information related to an individual, or a combination of pieces of information that could reasonably allow an individual to be identified. Personal information may consist of full name, personal contact numbers, residential address, email address, gender or date of birth. While information such as date of birth in isolation may not be enough to uniquely identify an individual, a combination of full name and date of birth may be sufficient to do so. 

Sensitive personal information is such personal information that is collected, received, stored, transmitted or processed by Marico, consisting of: 

  1. Password;
  2. User details as provided at the time of registration or thereafter;
  3. Financial information such as Bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details;
  4. Call data records;
  5. Physical, physiological and mental health condition;
  6. Sexual orientation;
  7. Medical records and history;
  8. Biometric information;
  9. Any detail relating to the above personal information categories as provided to Marico for providing service; and
  10. Any of the information received under above personal information categories by Marico for processing, stored or processed under lawful contract or otherwise.

The ownership of the sensitive personal information collected in this portal lies with the individual collecting the information. 

**Information We Collect**

We may collect personal information on this online portal voluntarily submitted by the user, including information we collect while performing business transactions and information we collect from other sources (as permitted by law). 

The following are examples of information we may collect directly: 

  * Name, email address, postal address
  * Username and password
  * Phone number or mobile number
  * Photo identity proof
  * Date of birth
  * Demographic information and service history
  * Payment instrument details (such as a credit card information, credit history, security codes) 
  * Future communication preferences

**How We Use This Information**

Personal information collected from data subjects listed in this portal will only be kept in order to conduct the required business, and for as long as the requirement was deemed at the time of data collection. 

The information collected may be used for the following activities: 

  * Create and manage information for master maintenance
  * Process payment for purchases or other services
  * Protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions
  * Enforce the terms and conditions of agreements, and otherwise lawfully manage our business.

**Access to Information by Relevant Persons**

All personal information must be accurate, complete, and relevant for the business purposes of collection of such information, and necessary only to facilitate those purposes. Your access to and use of this web-portal and its contents (the "Portal") is subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and all applicable laws. By accessing and using this Portal, you (the "User" or "you") accept and agree to these without any limitation or qualification. 

**Information Sharing**

We share personal information within Marico, and externally only as described below: 

  * Third-party service providers - We rely on third-party service providers to perform various services on our behalf. In order to perform these services, we may need to share personal information with them. 
  * Legal action and obligations - We may disclose personal information: 
    * Where permitted by law, to protect and defend the rights and property of Marico (including enforcement of valid agreements).
    * When required by law or public authorities.

**Information Security**

We are committed to keeping personal information secure. We limit access to personal information only to those who have a business need. We keep personal information only for the duration of valid business requirements or as required by law. 

**Changes to our Privacy Notice**

We will post changes to this privacy notice and update the effective date when this Privacy Policy is updated. We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, in our sole discretion and all modifications will be effective immediately upon our posting of the modifications. 

**Contact Us**

If you have questions or concerns regarding Marico’s privacy practices, please contact the Grievance Officer. The Grievance Officer shall respond to valid information requests and complaints within the statutory timeframe. 

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below: 

Grievance Officer Name : Mr. Satish Pai 

Company Address : Marico Limited, 7th Floor, Grande Palladium, 175 CST Road, Kalina, Santacruz (East), Mumbai – 400 098, Maharashtra, India. 

Email address : paisatish@maricoindia.net   
Contact telephone number :+91 9820332305 

_[from: 9:30 AM to 5:30 PM from Monday to Friday except Public, National & Festival Holidays]_

**Consent**

I acknowledge and agree to the terms contained in this data privacy notice, which shall be effective for the entire duration of my relationship with Marico as a user of this online portal and until Marico retains records of the captured personal information as specified above.
